Sometimes but sad, sometimes you are a little angry, sometimes you are happy-
-Int is you angry ... all emotions are totally okay to feel.
Come to school as you are.
I think that when the pondering becomes so tangible for one-
-That it takes over a little too much, so you don't get energy-
— maybe do other activities, or that you get a little powerless-
-Then I think it's a sign that it's time to go and talk to someone.
But again, I would really like to say: come and talk to adults.
About big and small.
One should probably never be afraid to put words into how to feel-
-And how to do it.
Is it that ...
... that you need help.
If one is a little afraid to put word-
-and start processes, so maybe it is still a sign on-
-That you need to talk to an adult.
Then you may need support in moving on.
An important thing to know if one comes to a curator-
-This is that we have a professional ethical duty of confidentiality.
That means what you tell me it will stay with me.
Unless you are in any kind of danger.
Then I have to take it further.